<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ming&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://minhdung.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ming&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://minhdung.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Du lịch Bangkok: Di chuyển (P2)</title>
      <link>https://minhdung.me/post/bangkok-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minhdung.me/post/bangkok-part-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tiếp tục với phần 1, phần 2 này sẽ nói về di chuyển đi lại trong chuyến đi. Tóm tắt cho ai ngại đọc: Đi bộ nhiều, Taxi tắc đường rất lâu, xe bus rẻ nhưng nhân viên và chỉ dẫn đều bằng tiếng Thái, BTS/MRT: hiện đại, đông nhưng rất nhanh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Du lịch Bangkok: Không giống review (P1)</title>
      <link>https://minhdung.me/post/bangkok-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minhdung.me/post/bangkok-part-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chào mọi người, bài viết này sẽ không như các bài review trên mạng đậm màu hồng và tươi đẹp về du lịch ở Thái Lan :D. Nội dung bài viết về chuyến hành trình của mình, từ lúc đặt vé máy bay tới khi đặt chân về phòng.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic HTML Elements</title>
      <link>https://minhdung.me/post/basic-elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minhdung.me/post/basic-elements/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The main purpose of this article is to make sure that all basic HTML Elements are decorated with CSS so as to not miss any possible elements when creating new themes for Hugo.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://minhdung.me/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minhdung.me/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Hugo</title>
      <link>https://minhdung.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://minhdung.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.
Setup Some fun facts about Hugo:
 Built in Go Loosely inspired by Jekyll Primarily developed by spf13 on the train while commuting to and from Manhattan. Coded in Vim using spf13-vim  Have questions or suggestions?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>